People.
I have been obsessed with this game ever since I played last.
I can't stop thinking about it.
I'm going straight in.
Continue.
I don't remember where...
okay I was at the beginning.
I am obsessed.
I've been thinking about this all the time.
I can't wait to play more.
I absolutely love experimenting with things.
Oh.
Look at that shit.
Wait, one and two?
Oh, it's just teaching me that.
Okay, okay.
Down with you.
I like how the tutorial is there every time you start the game.
It's just part of the temple or whatever.
It's kind of awesome.
I've decided that this is my favorite graphics in any of the 2D games I've played.
I absolutely love the style.
Like Hollow Knight was cool.
Rain World was amazing.
But I absolutely love this style for some reason.
There's just something about it.
It's so cool.
Of course, it also helps that there's this awesome physical simulation of all the pixels.
I just really love the look of it.
It's my jam.
What can I say?
Okay, today I will not die a single time.
I'm going to say this now.
By the way, I also started the stream a little earlier than usual because I just wanted to play this more.
I plan to play as long as I can.
It's just too good.
What do I have?
Hold on.
I have two wants.
One of them has an energy sphere.
In fact, it has two of them and someone's throwing dynamite it seems.
Let me go up here for safety.
And then I have three bombs.
That's nice.
Because that can destroy terrain.
The energy spheres?
A fast arcing projectile?
I don't think they can destroy... no.
There's no terrain destruction there.
So that's unfortunate.
That means I can't get to that gold.
That is sad.
But it is what it is.
We're going to play slow and cautious today.
And look for secrets.
Wait, is my character docking?
Oh, that's a cool little detail.
Look.
I'm not pressing anything.
It's doing that automatically.
Something is shaking a lot.
What the hell?
Is that just an explosion in the distance?
Shaking the screen?
Okay, that's oil.
I don't want oil.
And I want to find out what this does.
I can sort of eat things and we have a... your stomach is almost empty type deal here.
Okay.
Is this a bad idea?
Oh, hold on.
We got to go.
I think I can make it.
Hurry.
Tell me it's connected.
Fuck yeah.
Swimming in oil.
Levitation potion.
What?
Love that effect when you pick things up.
100% levitation.
Equip and throw.
Wait.
I had new keybinds for this.
Q.
Oh, it's making...
Holy shit.
That's a lot.
Whoa.
Holy shit.
That's big.
That's really big.
So if I walk on this, I'm affected.
Well, a little bit.
It's not much, but... So hold on.
If I now go into the oil... Wait a minute.
Let's say I do this first.
There.
Into the oil we go.
Ah, but then it's gone because we're in the oil, of course.
I should have thought about that.
But what if I drink it?
Wait a minute.
I have now drunk a lot of it.
Do I feel lighter?
I'm definitely slippery still because of the oil.
Okay.
I don't understand these big barrels of oil that just hang out here.
I like this one.
This is a great one.
Sir?
Come here.
Fuck yeah.
One shot.
Wait, how much damage does this do?
Five damage, damage slice?
I guess that means when it goes through enemies.
Whoa.
It was just a vine.
We're fine.
Speed 450 spread.
I need to start to pay attention to all these stats, by the way.
Because notice how even the wands have different stats.
In combination with the spells, it can be very different.
Why are you up there?
Fine.
You can stay there if you want.
Okay, that's a dead end.
How about I go above the big barrel of oil then?
Up.
Good.
God, the movement is so good.
Okay, now we're going to go right.
Push the mine cart.
We've got a dude down there.
Got him.
Perfect aim.
It's off to a good start.
We have 35 bucks.
Not quite enough for the things I have in mind.
Oh, I can also go through here.
I'm going to do that.
Oh, man.
I can't wait to play more of this game.
I can't wait for later today when I know I'll be playing this still.
You ever get that feeling with a new game?
You're playing it, but you can't wait to play it more already.
Such a weird feeling.
It's like, dude, I'm playing it now.
Calm down.
I guess I want to clone of myself so I can play it again at the same time.
So I can play it doubly much.
Mushrooms.
Eat them.
Wait, that seemed poisonous, what I just ate.
That was a bit of a poisonous icon.
Oh, man.
I want to find more lore.
I found some lore last time about... Oh, I forgot the names now.
Someone talking about the art or something.
And they were sworn to secrecy or something, not to reveal anything or be very vague about it.
So that guy is clearly out for blood.
Missed.
Okay, okay, okay.
This doesn't bounce, does it?
It does actually bounce.
Got him.
Oh, that's a lot of explosions right there.
Got it.
There's another guy right below here somewhere.
Oh, there's gold.
Oh, I forgot the gold disappears.
That's a thing, isn't it?
Shit.
What do we have over here?
Oh, wait.
This is the same spot though.
Is it not?
Tabula Smarardina.
If all the mountains were silver and gold, what would they profit?
A man who lives in constant fear of death.
This is the same tablet I found last time.
Hence, there cannot be in the whole world anything better than our medicine, which has power to heal all the diseases of the flesh.
Why do I have a feeling this medicine is something bad or like a trade-off?
Oh, I can even... Oh, I can actually pick it up too.
Wait, what?
Oh, I can throw it.
Maybe I have to take that with me.
Maybe if I collect all of the tablets, something will happen.
Look at that shot.
Come here.
Put this at... Yeah, okay.
Oh, I only have slots for one more, I guess, if I find another tablet.
That's unfortunate.
Okay, so there's the portal.
Very good.
So now I know that.
Let's not go there yet.
I need to find more money first, of course.
And I see enemies up here and a bunch of explodey casks.
Oh, that thing is right on top of one of them.
And we have a dude with a hat on.
No, wait, that's just water icon, never mind.
Is he gonna come up here?
Come here.
I know you want to.
Oh!
He was just about to shoot.
I heard the reload.
Or the loading of the gun.
Okay, so last time I died in the lava, I somehow fell through my little stuff here.
Wait!
Levitation.
Let's see how good it is.
Oh, it's actually insane!
Whoa!
Hold on!
Okay.
Uh, okay.
Oh, it's actually let's do a bit of water first.
This is safe to walk on, right?
I'm so scared that it's not safe.
I don't trust it.
Hold on.
Oh, wait, I see.
This is steam collecting at the top.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Yes.
Keep doing this.
Yeah.
I'm gonna douse myself in this.
We're gonna try.
Just do a lot of it.
There we go.
Look at that.
Look at that shit.
Okay.
Let's try it.
Oh.
Wait, what's up here?
Maybe there's something up there.
I'm not sure.
Oh, a bridge.
Why do I have a feeling this thing is gonna fucking collapse?
Let's be ready to fly.
Okay, never mind.
They just always do that in games.
Entered orb room.
Emerald tablet.
Volume seven.
And a red cloud with lightning.
Okay.
Among those who devote themselves to the transmutation of metals.
However, there can be no such thing as mediocrity or attainment.
A person who studies this art must have either everything or nothing.
An alchemist who knows only half their craft reaps nothing but disappointment and waste of time and money.
Moreover, they lay themselves open to the mockery of those who despise our art.
Those indeed who succeed in reaching the goal or the magistery have not only infinite riches but the means of continued life and health.
Hence, it is the most popular of all pursuits.
Transmutation of metals.
Definitely alchemisty.
It's like making gold, right?
Out of other things.
So don't go halfway.
Go all, go full way.
There's more.
Got it.
And again, art.
The art.
It's capitalized.
I think the art is something specific here.
Those who succeed in reaching the gold of the magistery have not only infinite riches, I guess because of all the gold, but the means of continued life and health.
Okay.
Yoink.
That's mine.
You discovered an orb of true knowledge.
I forgot.
Man, it's so quick I didn't get to read the other part.
Oh, press E to pick thundercloud.
Got it.
Five shots of this.
Creates a stormy cloud.
Static projectile.
Five uses.
90 mana drain.
That's all.
What's happening?
Oh, this is like a, like an amphitheater.
Isn't it?
These are places to sit.
And this is like the stage.
Everything is very golden here too.
We just have a couple of baths on the other side.
Wait a minute.
What do we have up here?
Whoops.
Oh, I thought I could stand on that.
What?
I can't stand on that?
Oh, that was bamboozled.
That totally looks like something you can stand on.
But I can go up here it seems.
Do I want to go up here?
So I can't actually use this right now.
Because I can't put it in my wand.
I need to be at the start.
Oh, can I just go back?
Actually, I wonder.
Oh no!
I thought I was stuck.
Huh.
Interesting.
Oh!
Uh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, there's a boss.
We're bossing.
Oh shit.
You know what I need?
I need levitatium.
Oh, I'm flying sheep.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Don't take a bath now.
Avoid, avoid, avoid.
Douse, douse, douse.
Get him.
I should just hold down the button, honestly.
Cause of death.
Sauvuyen tundiya.
Oh my god.
That was brutal.
Okay.
Alright.
Well, remember, the first death doesn't count.
Alright then.
The game is like, welcome back motherfucker.
Have fun.
So there's a boss over there.
Okay, I have spark bolt now.
And a fire bolt.
Remind me, does this...
It does a little bit of environmental destruction.
And that's important.
Hold on, there was...
You know what?
I'm gonna go grab that egg thing.
Because maybe I can use that.
And there's also stuff up here that I'm not quite certain about yet.
But there was something there.
I'm gonna go back over here now.
And there's also this curse thing going on, on this side.
I wonder if I can... So last time I grabbed something.
It was like three times the amount of gold, I think.
But I got cursed for it.
So I wonder if I can do that without getting cursed.
Wiggling egg.
I have it.
Oh, there it is again.
Diamond brickwork.
It took...
Maybe it's a different type of curse.
Curse of greed.
You gain three times gold but are terribly cursed.
Okay, gotcha.
But how am I cursed?
The curse has reactivated.
Oh, not that again.
Okay, so maybe it is the same thing every time.
So now, okay.
The mission now is to get to the portal ASAP.
Hopefully this curse is gone by then.
Maybe that's all it takes.
Get to the portal.
This is not a training.
This is real.
It's happening.
It's speed runtime.
And I have a decent wand as well.
I even have this, which is nice.
Is it actually following me still?
I'm not sure.
Why did it say curse reactivated?
Okay, we use the curse at least.
You know, get something for money here, so to speak.
Grab it, grab it.
Okay, that's getting a little too close.
Shit!
It's gonna explode, isn't it?
Yeah, I'm so fucking dead.
Why am I not dead?
Oh no!
Fuck.
I should have just gone for the portal.
But why did I try to kill these guys?
That was a mistake.
I knew it was a mistake.
I knew it!
Okay, okay.
All right.
So that's how it's gonna be.
Well, these deaths only fuel me more.
I need to get in there.
What do I have now?
Energy spheres and three bombs.
Okay.
We can do this.
I wonder if there's a way to get back to earlier areas.
I wonder if there's a way to get back to later areas.
Oh!
Sir?
Gotcha!
Okay, we're playing it safe again.
I also just realized I should have probably tried to... No, never mind.
I was about to say something dumb.
I was about to say that I should have tried the rain cloud thing I got against the boss, but I couldn't because it was a spell and it needs to be on a wand.
And I couldn't do that.
So, yeah.
I couldn't have done that, so that's fine.
Kill him before he throws anything.
And that guy... Oh my god, come on.
There we go.
Now we grab the gold.
Lots of nice gold.
There is a potion, I think.
If it's the small particle, it's a potion.
If it's the big particle, it's a wand.
Ah!
I got him.
It was a little bit risky there, but everything's fine.
Is that a chest?
Hello?
That looks like it.
That looks like a chest to me.
I'm going to go try and grab that.
What the fuck?
I'm going to try and grab it.
I know how to get there, too.
Oh, but do I, though?
I don't have the thing that can destroy the wall like I did last time.
Unless... Jesus!
That was a bad idea.
That was not a great idea.
What do I even have here?
Polymorphine.
Oh, wait a minute.
I have an idea.
I was hoping for something that could... Oh.
No, I thought I could fly.
I guess I still have the same amount of levitation power.
Let's try and see what else we can do.
Oh, it's this... Wait, this is different.
This is bad.
That's not good.
But wait a minute.
I do actually see a little... a little ledge there.
Can I not utilize that?
Come on, come on.
Let's try again.
Why am I always a sheep?
Huh.
Last time it was something different.
Oh, wait a minute.
Last time I had chaotic polymorphine.
Didn't I?
So this one is...
oh, polymorph.
It's always a sheep.
It's just like World of Warcraft, then.
Okay.
I think I understand.
That makes a lot of sense.
Shit!
Oh, well.
At least I realized that.
That's important knowledge.
And maybe with my two bombs remaining, I can find a way to the surface through over here.
You know, it's not that far off.
It's like right up here.
It's like this amount of... Ah, man, that's gonna be difficult.
Probably not happening.
But maybe we'll find a wand with something nice.
Let's just keep exploring.
Yoink!
Levitating sniper is what I am.
Gotcha.
Wait, where's your gold?
That's a wand.
Jesus!
Oh, this is the guy.
He's killing them!
Yo, that's great!
Thanks!
He's gonna burn alive now, too.
Oh, that's toxic rock.
Got him.
Oh, I missed that one gold piece.
That is pheromone potion.
Hmm.
I do wonder if I can use that to distract the boss.
You know, throw the pheromone...
make a little pool of pheromone potion and maybe it will be attracted to that and I can just stand there and DPS it.
What was I doing just now?
Right.
Wand.
Oh, I missed that one.
Oh!
Douse!
Oh, no wait, this is the wrong douse, but that's actually fine.
I mean, it works.
It removes the fire, so... not bad.
I do wonder if I'm... if the enemies are aggressive towards me when I'm a sheep.
Let's try this stuff.
Pheromone potion.
Oh, I can't get if I can distract some enemies with it.
Hey, dude!
Watch that!
Yeah, you like that?
Lots of pheromones over here.
You are attracted to it.
Oh, maybe not.
Okay, gotcha.
It was worth the test.
We gotta try with different animals, though.
Let's try with this one.
Nah, it doesn't look like it.
I got him, though.
Is he gonna explode in some kind of toxic shit?
I forgot.
Oops!
That was close.
Okay.
What do we have here?
Man, how do I get to that wand on the left?
I guess I could blow my way through.
Or maybe this is it, actually.
Go like this, and then we go up.
There's a bunch of enemies here, it seems.
Want to kill this guy?
Dude, I think I... this is my favorite wand so far.
This weapon does a sick amount of damage, and it's super accurate, and it's super predictable.
I love it.
Everything's burning up there.
There it
is.
We're close.
I'm so excited.
Oh, what the fuck is that?
Oh, it's one of those guys.
He looked different.
Fucking hell.
Okay, dude.
Shit.
I got blown up, and I had to escape because there was a bomb, and then the other guy took care of me.
That was the death duo right there.
Shit.
Okay, but now that we have three bombs, we can probably do some good digging now.
Hey, look, it's rolling!
Hey!
That's awesome.
I think it just set fire or something.
This wand is also okay.
It's not as good as the other one, but it's decent.
I need to ASAP find more wands, because that is the good shit.
Find more spells and stuff.
This always seems the same, by the way.
Like this little area here is always the same, it seems.
So there is definitely RNG in this, but it's like limited.
Ooh, that's a chest!
And there is a hooded figure next to it.
And one of these fuckers.
A mage!
I'm scared.
He's going to obviously throw fire at me.
Hold on, what do I even have here?
Slime potion.
Wait!
That protects me from fire!
Right?
Slime enclosed will take you from fire.
The mukus makes moving around difficult?
Fill me up completely.
Maximum slimeage.
Sir, I have now become immune to slime.
I mean, fire.
Actually, it doesn't work as well as I thought it would, but it definitely works.
I ate a fireball straight to the head.
That was pretty good.
Get him!
Oh!
Man, he shoots fast too.
Gotcha!
Drops three of them!
Good stuff, good stuff.
That is... I don't know what that is.
What does it say?
Ukuskivi.
Huh?
Wait, why is this glowing like this?
Look!
What the hell?
And there is the hooded figure.
Oh, he throws fire bombs.
I actually damaged the bottle in the air there.
He's dying though from that, you know?
He's in the toxic.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, he's dead.
He's dead.
But how am I going to get this?
Fill it up with this.
Oh, that was bad!
I'm going to die.
Oh, no!
The greed!
Okay, new rule.
Okay, I got to play this in a new way.
If something looks like I'm about to die, and it's going to be a little greedy, I will choose to disregard the greed, and I will be safe from now on.
That is the new rule.
No more greediness like that, because that was totally my own fault.
I was like, oh, look!
That's fire!
And that's toxic shit!
And it was just hell itself.
But then I saw the money.
Oh, look at this!
Extra max HP!
The game is throwing me a bone!
Awesome!
That's a good start.
Now I can't waste it, so we have to play safe now.
That's a cool start.
Worm pheromone potion.
I'll take it.
And what do we have again?
We have pheromone and worm... what if I mix them?
Wait a minute.
We're going to do some mad scientist stuff now.
Here's a little... let me kill that guy.
We're going to mix the pheromones.
It's not like... it just doesn't mix.
One is more dense than the other.
Gotcha!
What just happened?
Oh, I hear someone throwing.
That guy.
Oh my god, my wand doesn't even reach that far.
Got him!
Very cool.
Destroy this.
Make some holes in the terrain.
I do enjoy holes.
Especially the ones that can be plugged, you know it.
No, no, no, no!
Douse, douse, douse!
Oh man, I just lost a bunch of HP.
That was terrible.
Okay, so we have a potion in the water there.
Hey dude.
Okay, there's fire there.
We're not going to be greedy.
We're going to...
I thought he couldn't shoot me from there.
I thought there was a wall in between us.
Interesting.
But I got him.
That was very, very scary.
We're back though.
What's up guys?
Gotcha!
78 gold, that's a good start.
Not bad at all.
Blood and brickwork.
Okay, so I think I came from over here, didn't I?
I came from over there.
What does this mean again?
A charm affects you.
Let me affect myself more.
I just want to see if this has some kind of effect on anything.
I mean, obviously it has somehow.
A charm affects you.
Maybe I can charm...
maybe if I'm charmed and a certain enemy's charmed, they can become my companion.
Wouldn't that be cool?
I'm going to try and douse an enemy in this.
So I appoint you my friend.
Oh!
Okay, never mind.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, look.
He's affected.
Come here.
Yeah, get in there.
So now a charm affects him.
Is he on my side?
Sir?
Are you my friend?
Where you are?
Look!
He's my friend!
Let's go, buddy!
I was right!
Oh!
Oh, thank God there's a wall in between us.
I was looking down the barrel of that shotgun just now.
I saw my own death.
Fuck yeah.
Hey, come with me, dude.
Come on, Timmy.
This way.
We've got enemies here.
I took care of it myself.
You're too slow.
I wonder how long this lasts, though.
Hopefully it lasts forever.
Or until he dies.
Is he even coming with me?
Should not be standing up.
Wait, wait, wait.
Copper pouch.
A handy pouch for carrying powdery materials.
Copper?
Huh.
Copper.
Okay.
I'm thinking about alchemy now and how you can't go halfway.
You have to go the full way if you want to not be made a mockery of, right?
Oh, that's risky.
That turned out to be nothing.
Great.
Can I even make this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Definitely, definitely.
Easy, easy.
Let's keep going.
This is still the run where we got extra HP.
Let's play it safe.
What do we have there?
Broken wand?
Whiskey?
Wait, wait, what?
This wand has snapped in half, but it still crackles with magical energy.
Really?
Wait, what was my keybind for tea?
Is this gonna... Man, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I see sparks emanating from it and I'm wet.
Is this gonna electrocute me?
Let me get on wet first.
I have a feeling this is gonna be real bad.
Oh, someone's on the left.
Okay, water's gone.
Oh, but it's crackling.
Fuck, let's try it.
Oh!
Oh shit, I was not expecting to throw it.
What the fuck?
I thought I would be shooting it.
Interesting.
Okay, I'll be using... Watch this, we can do stuff like this then.
Fuck you.
Yeah, it's like a grenade, basically.
A very chaotic grenade.
That's awesome.
Hey dude, that's for you.
He straight up died from that.
I hit him in the face.
Oh god, not this dude.
So, I'm scared about this oil right here, and there's a fire dude.
That's a bad combination, right?
How about we... What is this?
The worm fer... Can I replace this with worm pheromone?
Fill it up.
All the way.
Actually, whatever, it's fine.
I'm definitely... I'm worm food.
Yeah, that's not good.
Where's the dude?
Where did the dude go?
Phew.
Scary stuff.
Wait, they...
they died?
I think they burned alive.
Nice, thanks for the money.
Look, they're hunting the monsters.
Gotcha.
Sick.
Okay, actually, I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to do that.
Actually, I want to go up here.
I see a gold nugget.
Rabbit!
Aha!
Got it.
That was not risky, because this was just blood.
No risks were taken.
I killed you.
Okay.
What do we have here?
A bunch of not good material.
God, I love the combat.
It's so responsive and smooth.
These are the... Oh man, how do I get in there?
I want to teach them a lesson.
Whee!
Look at that.
Perfection.
Ooh, rusted metal.
What the hell is this?
Oh, it's a mine cart.
It looked very different.
Eat the mine cart.
Very crunchy.
I do want to eat the mine cart.
Huh?
The gold nugget went through the ground to the upstairs.
That's interesting.
Oh, you know what?
Since I'm here, I want to fill this with water.
In fact, I want to get rid of all the pheromone shit.
I feel like water is more important.
There.
Pure water now, I think.
That's like my protection against fire.
In fact, I could have two of these with water.
Maximum water.
What if I put copper in water?
I mean, probably nothing's going to happen.
It's just sort of... floats to the bottom.
Nice.
Okay.
What if I put copper in here?
I want to just try different combinations of things.
I have a feeling that will produce something at some point.
That's a dead end.
So I go... wait.
Oh, it's an explodey barrel inside the coal.
Why do we have music?
We still had a fire dude down here, right?
That's what's worrying me right now.
Also, how do I get to these guys?
Do I even want to get in there is the question.
I mean, look at him.
You know what?
Yes, I do actually.
Because watch this.
They're gonna die.
Well, not quite, I guess, but almost.
Can they set each other on fire?
They are taking damage, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look, they're burning.
Yeah, one of them died.
It's only dynamite people left.
One down.
I think the other one died up here as well.
Oh, got it.
Whatever that was.
I don't know what it was, but I got it.
Levitation potion.
That's a good one.
I do love me some levitation.
What if I were to douse that on the enemies?
Will they levitate?
Okay, we've got enemies.
Oh, just a bunch of gold there.
Thank you.
327, by the way.
We are rich.
Let's check up here.
Okay, there's nothing there.
Oh, we got a big dude.
Big dude, big dude, big dude.
Watch.
That's for you.
Boom.
I don't think he died from that.
I think, yeah.
Go!
I think this guy spawns the little ones, right?
So this is going to be a little tricky.
I'm going to take care of these first.
There we go.
Let's check every door and every corner.
Doors and corners.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh!
Douse, douse, douse, douse, douse, douse.
Jesus.
That was scary.
We barely made it.
Okay.
There's a dude below me.
He's a dynamite man.
I can get him.
He's going to kill himself.
Yeah, kill yourself.
You idiot!
Gotcha.
Honestly, wait for the fire to subside.
You know what?
I ignore that gold.
We are sticking to the principle of not being greedy.
We ignore that.
And there's a bunch of poison here as well.
That is a bad path to take.
So we go another way.
I think I still see some poison here.
Oh!
God damn!
He almost got me.
Dynamite dude.
Haha.
Gotcha.
Did he throw a dynamite before he died?
He didn't.
Good.
Okay.
There's blood below me.
We can bathe in that a bit, I guess.
Make us resistant to fire.
We got to find that portal, dude.
What do we have below?
Is that it?
Get rid of the fire.
Seems like that fire burns eternally somehow.
Okay.
Enemy over there?
Oh, here it is.
I think I should just go through.
Yep.
Success.
That was a great first area.
Ah, you know what?
Take it now.
I'm too scared.
I'm not taking the other one yet.
Okay.
Let's see what we got here.
Oh, these are just spells.
Yeah.
Luminous drill.
I do like the idea of a drill with timer.
I need to find out what these things mean.
Rock.
Three.
Sea of flammable gas.
That's good.
Odd.
Firebolt.
And another rock.
Glittering field.
Firebolt with trigger.
I've seen this before with trigger.
There's almost a bomb that destroys... No, wait.
A bouncy explosive bolt that casts another spell upon collision.
Wait a minute.
Oh, that's not a bomb.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
So that just does that.
If I do this... Oh, wait.
There's also this stuff.
I have to look at this here.
Wait a minute.
So when it shows these two, it means it activated both of them, right?
Because I see... Oh, wait a minute.
Ha!
Wait a minute.
What?
Ha!
Wait a sec.
Okay.
So when this collides with the wall, it triggers that one.
Because watch.
If I just do a big arc, watch for this one.
It's not actually gonna happen.
Until it hits.
What if I do this?
That's weird.
So not only does it trigger the thing upon collision, but it shoots it from the point of impact, too.
Oh, wait.
What?
Okay.
That's... I don't understand that then.
So it... Oh, that is very weird.
I'm not sure I understand this.
Hold on.
Let me try some more.
Luminous drill with timer.
I feel like that sounds worse than a luminous drill.
Also, it's more cheap.
Oh, wait.
This costs 60?
This costs 30.
Luminous drill.
A pinpointed, short-ranged beam of concentrated light.
Okay.
Oh, right.
That is definitely a drill.
A luminous one at that.
So hold on.
If I put this here instead...
Oh.
Wait.
Wow, my mana recharge is slowly.
Wait, what?
Mana charge speed eight?
26.
Wow, it depends a lot on the wand.
Jesus.
But it cuts much faster, I guess, in that little time frame.
Okay.
So hold on.
What if I do this?
Okay.
So hold on.
What if I do this?
Also, this does spells per cast one.
So this should actually do the drill, and then this one as the second one.
With how much delay?
I think... 0.23 seconds?
Wait, what?
Wow, that does nothing.
Why is that?
What if I do this?
Ha!
Oh, I'm an idiot.
What if I do it?
I have the wrong thing on.
Okay, change it.
Oh!
Dude, the order is so important.
So this will... Okay, so luminous drill has a cast delay of minus 0.58.
With a recharge time of 0.17.
Minus 0.17.
What does that mean?
Does that mean it's reducing the recharge time on this one?
This is the base, and this is the thing that affects it?
Also, I have to remember, some of these are called projectiles in type, and some are modifiers.
I had one last time that was a modifier, remember?
And multicast as well.
So if I do this... I mean, you can dig with this, I guess.
Yeah, that one is not good.
What if I do this one?
But it's terrible, because the mana recharge is terrible.
This is definitely the superior version, I think.
Okay, what else do I have?
Glittering field.
Static projectile.
Small explosions appear randomly over a large area.
I don't know about that, dude.
That seems a little...
Wow!
I'm not pressing anything.
Wow, that keeps going for a while.
Damn, I guess it's nice if you have a bunch of enemies around you, and you just wanna throw it off, you know?
Put that out there, and then just run away.
Maybe just keep shooting this while you run from them, you know?
And have them walk through the chaos.
Maybe something like that.
But if I combine this with that... So this means... Oh, dude!
Dude!
I can aim this now, I think.
Watch!
I'm gonna shoot this?
This is gonna arc, and when it lands, it's gonna spawn the glittering shit.
Watch.
Oh, wait, no!
Hold on.
Maybe it took too long.
Oh,
no, I don't understand then.
Shit!
Oh, static projectile.
Oh, what?
Maybe change that?
No, that's just gonna... Right.
Okay.
That would have been cool, though.
Right?
This does cast another spell upon collision.
So I would think that this one would be cast at the location where this impacts.
But I guess I'm wrong.
I kinda... The issue is, I kinda want this luminous drill, but I only have two wants.
And it's kinda shit in the second one, you know?
It's like... And then I have to wait a million years?
That's useless.
Oh, it's 50% off.
That's why this is 30.
Luminous drill with timer.
So what is the difference?
Let's try and understand this.
A pinpointed short-range beam of concentrated light that casts another spell after a timer runs out.
Okay.
How long, though?
Cast delay minus 0.58?
What if I do this?
Oh.
Okay.
So it is actually almost like firework, you know?
You shoot up a rocket.
Usually you set a timer for the... or you build the little payload to have certain parts of the payload explode at certain times.
But I'm not sure... All of these have cast delays stats on them, which is very weird.
With timer.
But why would I have a luminous...
Okay, I don't understand.
What's this?
That's the rock.
Odd firebolt.
See a flammable gas.
Rock.
Another luminous drill.
Man.
Drills everywhere.
I think I should use all my money, though.
Let's try the odd firebolt.
A somewhat peculiar bouncy explosive shot.
It has a little less damage.
And but more fire damage.
And it adds half a second cast delay.
Whatever that means.
Oh.
Oh, it goes like a little sine wave, I guess.
That's weird.
Or not.
It's like randomized.
Huh.
It's very unpredictable, I guess.
Yeah, very peculiar and bouncy.
Bouncy.
Huh.
Look at that.
It bounces on the water.
Okay, that is peculiar.
And then it explodes.
Wow.
Cool.
That's pretty neat.
Let's try the rock.
Let's see this.
It's literally just throwing a rock.
That better do some good damage, is all I'm saying.
I think I'm going to save the rest of my money.
No, you know what?
Get this one.
We're trying everything.
See a flammable gas.
Wait, why is there a warning sign on it?
That doesn't sound good.
Doesn't work.
Oh, mana drain 140.
Oh, I don't have enough mana for that.
Oh, I don't have I have 124.
Oh, I can't even use this.
Gotcha.
Okay.
All right.
Well, I think I've tried everything here.
So before I do anything else, let me click on this button over here to refill everything.
Hell yeah.
All spells refreshed.
And now we're going to make... I think I'm going to do a hard one.
Ah man, I wish I had more wants.
The fire bolts.
I got to go with the bomb, I think, for now.
It's just too good.
The digging potential, right?
Okay, what do we have here?
Hungry ghost summons a heavy minion who will eat enemy projectile every now and then.
That sounds pretty dope.
And looky minion summons a looky minion to your help.
Or unlimited... most spells are now unlimited?
What?
Yo, that seems sick.
Wait a minute.
Maybe I want to equip something else then.
Fire bolt with trigger.
How about we do that?
Just in case it gets unlimited?
Excuse me?
Oh my god!
Dude!
That's crazy!
What the fuck?
Oh!
The cold pits.
Oh shit!
I feel like this is going to fuck me up in the end because I'm going to be too trigger-happy.
Oh my god!
I thought it would throw it longer or farther.
I can't speak English.
Oh, this is unreliable now because I don't know which is shooting.
Ah, it's unreliable as fuck!
I hate this wand.
Oh, I can't go back, can I?
Oh no!
I fucked up, didn't I?
This is a bad wand.
I can't change it.
Shit.
Oh shit.
Well, I guess we're bombing.
Or unless, if we wait long enough, it should always be the fire bolt first.
Now I wait.
Shit.
Okay, so I just make sure to shoot one extra afterwards.
So I know the next one is going to be a fire.
That's so scuffed.
But it's okay.
It's okay.
Shit.
That is a concentrated mana potion.
Interesting.
Oh no!
I got you.
You're dead.
I should be able to blow this up now.
I have infinite bombs.
What an insane perk!
Wow, what is this?
Oh, it's concentrated.
What does that mean?
You gain mana back faster.
Let me pick some of that up.
Can I... what do I have in here?
Water and work through.
Get rid of all that.
Just drain it a little bit here.
Wow, I drained so hard I made the concentrated mana, dude.
Fuck yeah.
You gain... how much faster?
Oh, I can't really tell.
It's hard to tell.
So the next one should be a fireball now.
That's good.
Or a fire bolt.
Isn't it fire bolt?
It is a fire bolt.
Wait, what's this?
Hello?
Oh, it's a fire bolt.
Look!
There are things hidden.
What the fuck?
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Can I go back and blow shit up to make my way through again?
Shit.
Got him.
How do I get back up there?
What's the best way?
Oh, look at all the enemies here.
I don't understand.
Where did I come from?
Obviously not from the dark areas.
I came from up here.
I came from here.
Yeah, that's it.
Let me try something here.
Oh, just barely.
Not enough.
Maybe if I am a little more... Hey, that works.
Okay.
Okay, I'm going to try something here.
Concrete.
Nice!
For some reason, I was expecting this stuff to not be able to be destroyed, you know?
Hell yeah!
Okay.
Now we go over here.
Man, I can still go back and buy?
That's awesome!
No, wait, I can't get in.
No way.
Almost.
We are making an attempt to get in.
And progress?
Wedge that in there?
Shit.
Dude, that is very protected, isn't it?
Worm crystal.
Yeah, it's not doing much, is it?
Let me just try and blow everything to smithereens.
What can I destroy here?
Dude, infinite bombs is crazy good.
What the fuck?
That is like a next level perk compared to everything else.
This is all very immune to damage.
I must say.
Very good craftsmanship in this place.
I'm stuck!
I couldn't move for some reason.
What the fuck?
That was scary as fuck.
Oh my god.
Okay, so let me build that up.
Oh!
Okay.
Why does this collapse when I walk through?
Okay, well, now I know that.
That's not going to work.
That's for you.
This is going to be so much fun.
This is the best thing ever.
Six shot there.
Don't hit me.
Don't even think about it.
There we go.
Oh man, I hate these little pieces of ground that is hard to tell what is part of the background, what is not when you destroy things.
Shit.
Ah!
I hate this weapon so much.
We need to replace this ASAP.
Dude, we can dig for gold.
It's got... What the hell is that up there?
Oh, it's one of those that blade lava, isn't it?
Damn, dude.
Hahaha!
Fuck yeah.
We're blowing everything up.
That's amazing.
There you go, buddies.
Oh!
Wow!
That's amazing.
There you go.
Wow!
I hit that bomb midair.
Okay, we've got a bunch of people here.
This is getting a little tricky.
Oh!
Hahaha!
This is too much fun.
Return to sender.
Shit!
I need to aim a little higher.
There we go.
Got him.
Okay.
Sick shot!
Look how I used the momentum to my advantage.
How did that just kill him?
Did it go there and bounce up?
That was interesting.
Gold for me.
I'm going to be so rich.
Oh!
I think that was a lamp.
It was just a lamp.
What do we have up here?
I think I'm going a little too quick.
Anything in here?
Not a bad idea to be wet all the time, honestly.
Got him.
Give me that gold.
And then I can dig over here now.
I'm going to destroy this entire level.
I'm not going to pass up this opportunity.
Hell naw.
We can go anywhere we want.
Almost anywhere, I guess.
What?
Huh?
Boomerang!
Why can I... What is this?
Magic bolt with timer?
Bounce?
Dude, what?
Bubble spark with... Wait a minute, what do I have now?
Spitter bolt.
I think bubble spark is the one I like, isn't it?
Bouncy... No, wait.
Inaccurate spell that casts another spell upon collision.
I'm going to come back here.
I'm going to collect gold and come back here.
Holy shit!
Look at all this gold!
Wait, what's down there?
What do we got there?
Explode that one.
Oh, we got a dude.
Got him.
Okay, we need some gold then.
I can blow this up.
Although that's going to be a little challenging.
Wait, did that just collapse a little bit from that?
I'm just blowing everything up.
Why do we get the music?
Shit.
What if I blow up coal?
Gold for me.
This is the best.
There are certain things that don't get destroyed by explosions, it seems.
It's like very odd, very angled explosions sometimes.
This brickwork is also slowly collapsing, it seems.
Whenever you ever shake the ground.
See, this didn't do much here.
Isn't that weird?
So this is grey rock.
It does nothing to grey rock.
Okay.
I think I need a different type of explosion to get through to that little special place in the start.
With the worm, whatever it was.
Remember?
Wait, what's this?
Oh, I guess there's so much coal because it's called the coal pits.
Makes a lot of sense.
Naturally that would be the case.
Whoop.
Bomb that.
200 gold already?
There's a dude in there.
Can I get in there?
Maybe via here.
That is a death trap for later, so I may as well blow that up.
Also, I do have this stuff.
Copper plus grass plus soil pouch.
Flammable at all?
Not really.
Collect it.
That's a rock.
Oh, oh my god.
Oh shit.
Get blown to pits.
Haha, yeah dude.
Maybe a bit of... Oh my god, how did I get you?
I need to play this safe.
I'm at 31 HP.
This ain't good.
Got him.
Thank you.
What the fuck is that?
What is that?
Okay, is he dead?
He's dead.
Look at all the gold though.
Oh, wow.
I'm fucking rich.
So there's a dude up there as well, I think.
I think that's for you sir.
Have fun with that.
Man, the infinite bombs.
Look at this guy.
I'm scared.
That's for you.
No, it's actually for me it seems.
Got him.
I don't know what he was about to do, but I'm afraid of it.
So if we don't know what it is, we kill it as fast as we can.
Because if it is dangerous, it's better to take out the danger quick.
This is so cool.
Oh, there's a bunch.
Hello.
I can't hit anything.
Oh my god.
Yikes.
Got him.
Not bad.
Slowly making progress in these treacherous lands.
Oh, yeah.
It's a wand.
A golden wand.
Wait.
Got him.
Okay, let's see what we got.
Homebringer teleport bolt.
Brings the target.
Hit closer to you.
Burning trail.
Another one.
Double scatters.
What is this?
Huh?
I'm scared of playing with it.
I feel like I'm going to die if I don't die.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is this?
Always casts chaotic path.
Causes a projectile to chaotically fly wherever it wishes.
I don't know about that one, man.
We're going to try it.
Oh, wait.
Is this self-harm?
No, it's not.
Okay.
No friendly fire.
That's great.
Because that means I can go in tight quarters and go brrr.
And everything is fine.
These spells are so cool.
I love them.
Look how big the wand is.
It's a big boy.
Is that a dude down there?
I love that it lights it up as well.
I saw a dude down here.
Come on.
Reveal thyself.
Let's also blow this up.
There's money there.
There's gold in them hills.
There we go.
That's good enough for me.
Let's wedge that in there.
Good.
Let's get in there.
There's stuff in here, it seems.
Oh, wait.
How much damage does this do?
Spells... three spells cast.
Five damage per projectile.
Awesome.
All right.
That's extremely dense rock.
I imagine it's not going to get destroyed by this.
Yep, I figured.
Or we can get through there and get some gold.
Dude, this run has been so fucking fun so far.
I haven't even gotten that far, but it's just so much fun.
Oops, wrong one.
I want this one.
Just look at that shit.
Is that not the coolest ever?
Damn, it's good.
It's super good.
Holy shit.
What do we have here?
Let's clear the way.
I don't know what's down there, so we blow it up.
Good mentality to have, I think.
More.
I see a guy down there.
I see him.
I think...
Oh!
Was that his head?
Did his head just fly up here?
That's incredible.
Fuck yeah.
Say night night.
Come on, come on.
Oh, this wand is incredible.
Huh?
Oh, that's a good one.
Okay.
I'm stuck, I'm stuck, I'm stuck, I'm stuck!
Water, water.
Oh, HP, HP, HP.
Oh, 185.
That's a big number.
Oh, 14 HP.
And there's another wand in there.
Oh, we're getting close to the point where I feel like I'm getting a little bit too eager here.
Good.
Oh, there you go.
What's falling from the ceiling?
Are we okay?
There's a wand right there and there's no enemies it seems.
Okay.
There's an enemy.
What if I shoot it like this?
Nah, it's not gonna seek him out or anything.
But I can do this.
That's for you, sir.
Fuck yeah!
What the hell is this?
A bouncing burst.
A very... Oh, but hold on.
I shouldn't discount this immediately.
Because maybe the wand has great stats.
That's what I should be thinking about here.
See, this one has 160 max mana.
Oh, but this one has 210.
Not bad either.
Capacity 6 mana charge speed 45.
This one can't do anything.
Okay.
So, I'm gonna go ahead and cast three spells though.
That's also interesting.
Oh, I don't know.
160 spells cast one.
Oh, there's also the shuffle thing.
Oh, once that shuffle cast their spells in random order.
I should mouse over this and see what it says.
The number of spells this wand casts when used.
Right.
The time between casts.
The time it takes for this wand to recharge when all spells inside it have been cast.
Okay.
Ah, okay.
So, cast delay is the time between the different spells in the wand.
But the recharge time is the... I guess the recharge time for the wand itself.
When that whole sequence has been completed.
Pretty cool.
The directional deviation of projectiles casted by this wand.
Ah, that's great.
Okay.
I don't think I want this.
This does not seem to have great stats.
Like, I pretty much always want cast delay and recharge time to be as low as possible, I guess.
Right.
There's no reason not to have them be super low.
0.83.
I'm gonna leave this here.
I do not believe in that wand.
Okay.
I think I have enough money to go through.
In fact, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Let's just quickly see what's over here.
Is this dumb?
Am I doing a dumb thing here?
Okay, we're going, we're going, we're going.
I'm too scared.
Fuck yeah.
We're doing it.
Heal up.
195 HP.
Not bad at all.
And what do we have?
A bunch of new things.
Add mana.
Bouncy burst.
Wait, circle of vigor?
Does that mean healing?
What?
Light?
Personal fireball thrower.
Okay.
Oh my God.
I got a sneeze.
Holy shit.
Fucking allergies.
Glowing lands.
All seeing.
That one is actually pretty nice.
Spitter bolts.
Explosion of spirits.
Okay.
I think I want this dude.
If this does what I think it does.
Oh, but it has two uses.
I think mana drain 80.
A field of regenerative magic.
Awesome.
Oh, but look, this one does have two uses.
It doesn't have infinite.
So unlimited spells does not apply to this because this also says most spells are now unlimited.
So that must mean this is a good one.
Right.
That goes here.
Actually the bombs are quite nice.
Oh, I'm going to be using.
Why are there so many in here though?
Isn't this completely insane?
Why are there so many?
Okay, I'm going to be doing a shit ton of testing now.
Let's take this one out for testing purposes now.
Let's just shoot this.
Okay.
What if I just remove some?
So it's the same but a little less.
That makes sense.
But does it even make sense to... Wait.
Wait a minute.
It says spells per cast two.
Oh, wait.
Wait a minute.
Cast delay.
Does that mean it shoots these two?
Pup delay.
These two pup delay.
These two pup delay and all the way through.
So 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2.
So this one is actually wasted I guess.
2, 4, 6, 8, 10.
If I remove this, I think that's what that means.
And then the recharge time.
1.13.
Yeah, look.
Yeah.
I know what that means.
I totally know what that means.
Okay.
And if I add this at the end, this should not fire.
Oh, it does.
Okay.
So I guess it just does a delay like normal and then it just cast one spell instead of two.
Yeah, of course it does.
Of course it does.
What if I put this here?
Oh, wait a minute.
Does that mean?
So this is a projectile modifier.
If I just shoot that on its own, nothing happens.
So it's modifying an existing projectile, right?
To have light.
But if I put this here, is it only going to modify one of them?
Oh, that's... Oh, this one.
So it's everything that comes after.
Or maybe not everything.
Maybe just one.
It's hard to know, I guess.
If I were to put this here, is this everything?
It is not.
Notice how these don't have light.
It's only the first one.
So this one has light.
The others don't.
Also, spells per cast too means it's going to cast the light and the bubble spark as one spell combined.
And then there's a cast delay and it goes to these two.
And then it keeps going and there's no light on any of these.
So if I had more light, I could technically put a light in between each if I wanted every one of them to have a light on them.
Right?
Okay.
What else do I have here?
Add mana.
Let's try that.
Add 30 mana to the wand.
And then I'm going to projectile modifier.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Why is that?
Oh, it adds a cast delay.
Okay.
So that's why there's a little delay in the beginning and then it continues as normal.
Pump, you know?
And it adds 30 mana when this batch is being sent.
Dude, this is so fucking, this is like really advanced stuff here.
Let me just fill this up with here because I don't have any room.
Can I delete spells that I don't want?
I wonder.
Bubble spark with trigger though.
A bouncy inaccurate spell like can't cast another spell upon collision.
So if I were to go this,
I think it's hard for me to tell what's happening here.
So let me get rid of these for now.
If I were to do that.
This one casts one spell per cast.
So it's used.
Pump, pump, pump.
But when this one collides with something, it casts another spell.
Oh wait, I can, let me see here.
If I were to go like this.
Ha!
Oh, that's weird.
If I were to do the mana thing here, I have to technically keep this going.
That is freaking awesome.
So this one, okay so this adds a cast delay.
Fire bolt, spitter bolt.
Let me just try a bunch of things here.
This is way too much fun.
She was the first one like that of course.
Burning trail.
Projectile modifier.
So that only affects one.
Unless this means that this doesn't take up a badge.
This affects the next badge because there's two per badge, right?
I guess I can test.
Let me maybe do it up here instead because it's easier for me to understand.
Wait, it doesn't work at all.
Oh, maybe, okay, okay so I think I understand then.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Yep.
So what this means is that this right here now has a burning trail.
Only this one.
The others don't.
Oh, I can, what if I do this?
What happens then?
Hold on.
Oh, it just skips what if I were to do that?
Huh, I guess it just skips spaces.
That's weird.
That's awesome though.
I like it.
So can I stack modifiers?
So this is a projectile modifier.
I don't think this works because spells per cast is only two.
It shoots... wait!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, I think I misunderstood something very basic here.
I have just reached an understanding I think.
Oh, I don't have enough space to... I have way too many spells.
I have way too many spells.
Shit.
Ah, man, I can't test properly with all these in here.
So wait, if I do this...
I guess I just need to press the mouse once.
No, so that's the second.
Ah, okay, wait a minute.
I need to look here.
So this is being added.
Why can't I mouse over it?
It's the... oh man, I can't point to it.
It's the one that always casts.
It's like the little chaotic thingy there.
So that is being done always.
Huh?
Okay, so that is being done on two of them now.
Fire mana two of them.
Fire mana... So now it's... it's done this.
So now it's going to do these two with the chaotic.
Shit.
Yeah.
So this is the first and one.
Two, two, two, one.
And then it starts over.
Ha!
I understand.
I understand what's happening.
I think.
So I wonder if there's a time... Let's say I don't use this wand for a long time.
Will it reset this whole thing?
You know?
So I go pop.
Now I wait.
I wait a long time.
And then I go... Shit.
Okay.
It doesn't reset.
And then one.
And starts over.
Okay.
So that means you can stack modifiers and they will affect... Oh shit, I'm burning!
Fuck!
I did not realize the burning trail could put myself on fire.
Okay, that's bad.
Oh god.
What was that?
I heard something.
Okay, whatever.
So basically what this means is that you can stack these modifiers and it will only affect the next batch.
So this means these two will affect this batch.
Right?
And all of that is being affected by the chaotic path or whatever that is inherent to this wand.
You see?
Pretty cool.
I don't like the burning trail because it has a chance of fuck me up and that's not good.
So if...
Oh, we're just getting started.
Wait.
Oh, I need to look here actually.
And?
Wait, what?
Oh, of course.
Yeah.
Wait.
Oh, I see it there up here.
Huh?
Maybe it needs to come after?
You know, it's definitely... it's definitely being used somehow.
Plus 10 degrees.
Multicast.
Okay, so simultaneously casts.
You know what?
Let's try it here.
That's probably easier.
Oh.
Okay, so now it's being shown here.
How is this simultaneously casting too?
Unless I need to.
Oh, okay.
If I remove this, they should always only throw one.
Yeah, because look, this has spells per cast one.
So this one right here is basically a modifier to the spells per cast.
You can circumvent that a little bit.
If I do this, you can always shoot two.
See that?
If I remove it, it's always just one.
Pum pum pum pum.
But with this one, it's way more.
Not bad.
Okay, what if I put it in the center?
Ha!
So it shoots one, and then it goes... Wait, does that mean it wraps?
Dapped up.
Wait, so it shoots that one, and then it uses this, that and that?
That one?
That and that?
Oh!
Interesting!
Look at that, it wraps around.
This one, when this... Okay, so it starts with this one, right?
Because it's spells per cast one.
And then the next spell is technically this one.
But this one casts two spells.
But notice how when I do it, that's the first, it uses two.
So that must mean it uses this one and the next.
But then it resets, because what comes after is the single.
Aha!
Okay.
This one is... I don't understand why I would ever do this.
If this does what I think it does, that seems like a really bad time.
Wait a minute, can I?
Oh yeah!
Wait, let me see this.
It definitely does bring it closer to me.
Look, it appears right at me.
Maybe that can be used if I have something very close range that was guaranteed to kill someone.
If I then hit them with this, follow it up with a massive, I don't know, something shotgunny, you know?
Just poof!
That could be something that could work.
But that seems too scary for me right now.
Okay, what else do I have here?
I don't want to go too crazy.
Actually, I do want to go crazy, because I have a bunch of money.
Burst of air?
Please do.
You definitely can!
Well, in that case, I don't need that many of these, because this one only casts... hold on.
So I can technically do this.
In the water you go.
If I do that,
so with trigger,
this is just going to start... is this bad?
Oh wait, no, I need these.
Wait, I have more, I have more.
I guess the more the better actually here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So do this.
Just fill this one up completely.
And we also had one over here, right?
Yep.
Grab that.
Oh, we also have perks there.
I can't wait to try those.
There.
This is going to be a crazy one!
Let's see.
Damn!
Okay, okay, we can make it even more crazy.
We can...
what if I... do like that?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, but it adds a castile of half a second.
So that's not... but what if I add this at the end though?
No, that's not good.
I don't like that.
I don't like it.
A short lift magical bolt.
This could be nice in the beginning honestly.
And the reason I say that is if I'm using this around the corner, that's going to do a lot of damage in the beginning, which is nice.
It's like a little shotgunny.
This is my wand down here for now.
That's my wand.
That's number four.
Let's try some more of these.
Personal fireball thrower.
Glowing lands.
I have 228, so I can pretty much buy two spells it seems.
No, I don't want that.
Bouncing bursts.
I think I want this one.
Glowing lands.
A magical lands that cuts through soft materials.
35 damage.
Oh, that looks nice.
That looks like one of those things that do a lot of damage.
We can add a fire trail to this.
Yep, we can definitely do that.
But if I do this... Oh no, no.
Yeah, I need two of these then.
Yeah, I need two of them.
So that's not going to help me here.
Firebolt with... Oh, wait a minute.
Yeah, I can.
And then it shoots the thing after.
Oh, that's chaotic though.
That's crazy.
Oh, man.
I could also put this down here.
What if I stack the triggers?
What then?
It shoots two?
So that means... If I replace this with that... Oh, no, wait.
No, no, no, no.
Because this has a huge cast delay.
It's terrible.
Terrible.
The glittering field.
That's just getting shot at the end, but at my location.
And I don't mind having the cast delay added on top at the end, because it's the end of my volley anyway.
I'm not intending to shoot more than one volley of this.
Right?
But if I add a trigger thing... Wait, a bouncy casts another... Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, if I do this... That should be crazy.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, it shoots both of these immediately, of course.
Damn, this lasts a long time, doesn't it?
So how would I do this?
What I'm trying to do is to have this thing appear where the first projectile lands, sort of.
So if I hit an enemy somewhere off in the distance, it's going to activate there.
You know what I mean?
So two spells per cast.
I understand that.
That means it's going to start using this, and that.
Those are getting fired at the same time.
So maybe I need to do this, because when this one... So it's shooting these two, but then when this one gets shot, it's going to collide somewhere and trigger that one.
And then it continues.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Look at that.
This is crazy, dude.
This game is nuts.
Look at this.
You're doing some crazy stuff.
Okay, okay.
I have infinite rocks.
Oh, and this one does three spells per cast, too.
Oh, my God.
Hold on a second.
A somewhat peculiar, bouncy explode.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if... Oh, dude.
I bring someone close and I throw a rock in their face.
Wait, there's no damage on it.
Huh?
How much damage does it do?
Oh, no.
Do I have anything else?
So this cast three per time, so that means I can do one more.
Something that would do a lot of damage up close.
This one, maybe.
Let's try this.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no, actually.
Wait, what?
Oh, wait.
Is that what's happening?
Oh, it only shoots a rock when I have 100 mana.
Otherwise, it just starts with the next batch.
Because when I held the button, no rocks came out.
Okay, dude, I am learning everything.
This is great.
I don't think I want this though.
This seems nuts.
But I kind of like the idea of shooting rocks.
I wish I had more rocks so I can shoot multiple rocks.
Let me see what else we got.
I've got lights.
I do like this one, but I can't... Oh, I don't have enough gold.
I guess I buy this.
Personal... You know what?
Before I buy more, I should probably have checked what these perks are.
Always cast one off.
A random always cast spell is added to the one in your hand.
Up to a maximum of four.
Ooh.
You get more critical hits?
That doesn't sound bad.
Your spells knock enemies around with more force.
Ha!
They all kind of sound intriguing.
This one sounds like the no-brainer if you want to stay consistent and you know, know what you're gonna get.
Except I don't know how much more critical hits I'm gonna get.
I think I want to try this with this wand.
We gotta try it.
A random always cast spell is added to the one in your hand.
I don't know what's...
Why can't I mouse over it?
I don't know what that is.
I can't see it.
How do I... Ah!
How do I actually do that?
I can't sort of pin it.
I mean mouse over!
Fuck!
It cast something...
Looks like Trifurcate.
If you know, you know from another game.
Huh?
You know what?
Let me remove this for a second because it's really fucked.
I think I like... Yeah.
Whoa!
Oh!
Wait!
Some of them are red, some of them are blue.
Oh, is this because I have red and blue spells.
No, no, no, no, no!
Some of them are red, some of them are blue.
Look at the red version and a blue version.
Maybe the blue ones heal them, the red ones damage them.
I don't know.
But it sounds crazy.
And you know what?
I think I will have a light.
Let's put a light here.
Just so we can see what the fuck is going on, you know?
I like that.
I like the light.
Although we could have also... Oh man.
Oh, this is too much fun.
I am gonna make a one with this one and light.
I think that could be really cool.
So this one right here is basically gonna be my number one damage dealer from now on.
This is my go to bread and butter thing.
This one down here, we're going to double scatter glittering.
Yeah, what if I do this?
What does that do?
Wait a minute.
Is that digging?
Oh no, wait, this is a projectile.
It's not a projectile.
I thought for a second I could make this have the properties of the drill itself.
That's what I thought.
Shit, okay.
But hold on, I have an idea.
If we now use this, this one here.
I run out of mana like that, but with this I don't.
Look, full mana.
I can technically dig.
Like this is digging.
Wait, can I?
No fucking way.
This is how I do it.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, dude.
So bombs don't work, but this does.
It's not very effective, but it works.
Oh, worm crystal.
Yeah.
Oh, it floats.
Can I pick it up?
Worm crystal.
Yeah.
Did I just hurt myself?
Is this breaking?
Holy shit.
Get out of here.
What the fuck is this?
The worm crystal is shattered.
You feel less safe.
Oh no.
I don't like that.
I don't like feeling less safe.
That does, that is... Oh, you know what?
Oh.
Dude.
Watch.
We're going to test this.
Because we can recharge.
It totally heals.
Oh my god.
That is awesome.
And then we can recharge it over here when we need to.
Fuck yeah.
That just occurred to me.
Okay.
See a flammable gas.
You know what?
I think I will have this in here.
This is going to be my heal.
That's my heal wand.
And that one will do... I don't even know.
I don't even know.
I don't even know that.
Why not?
I do like the bombs though.
Is that too crazy?
Wait a minute.
What a wand.
It's blowing up everything.
This is chaotic as fuck.
Also, you know what I'm scared of?
I'm scared of this spell that explodes everywhere.
It's going to accidentally trigger one of the numerous barrels that explode.
You know, it's going to be a cluster fuck.
That scares me a lot.
So you know what?
I'm taking this away.
That just occurred to me.
That's probably for the best.
So yeah.
I do like the bomb though.
But maybe not in that one.
This down here.
If I put this up here instead, how is this going to change?
It's terrible now.
And the reason is, recharge time is 1.13 seconds.
This is only 0.33 seconds.
Yeah, this is bad now.
I don't think I want the digging.
The digging sucks.
Does this cost mana?
I don't know.
It does.
So... Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can I make this super fast?
Okay, that's not super fast.
Can I make it faster somehow?
Luminous... I don't know if I can.
Probably not.
I mean, I may as well have this here, right?
Add the mana.
It costs 80 mana.
What do I want along with the bomb?
I think I'm good, honestly.
Let's buy one more thing and then let's head off.
I want this personal fireball thrower.
That seems awesome.
Makes a projectile turn the creatures it hits into living fireball throwers.
It's a modifier.
Oh, man.
Is this a terrible idea?
There's one of these projectiles.
If that hits an enemy, it's going to make them throw fireballs.
Let's not do that.
Let's put this here instead.
Here.
So if they get hit by this, this is my sniper.
Oh, this is a shitty recharge.
Why is that so slow?
What?
Oh, the mana is really bad on this.
Oh, it costs 90.
But you know what?
This can be my sniper.
If I hit something, pop!
Scrap!
Then they become fucking crazy things.
I like that idea.
And then we're going to have our bomb thing there with some light and a rock.
Oh, but wait, we can't because six... No, this doesn't cost any mana.
Hey, wait, this works?
Yeah.
Yeah, I like that.
I like the rock.
The rock is good.
Dwayne Johnson comes with us.
Okay, this is fucking fun.
I am ready to keep going, but I just need to take a quick piss and then we go.
Be right back.
Okay, let's keep going.
I'm excited.
I now have my basic wand here that will... It's my kill wand, basically.
And I will be safe using it, I think.
I'm not going to take damage.
Then we have the heal... Oh, wait, I got a recharge.
Then we have a heal wand, which is awesome.
Yep, it recharges it.
Oh my god, this is going swimmingly.
And then we have the bomb slash rock slash light wand and we have the sniper wand that turns enemies into fireball emitters or whatever.
So that excites me.
Let's fucking go.
Oh, we've got enemies already.
Oh, it's so good.
Snowy depths.
This is where I got fucked up last time.
By some mages, remember?
Oh,
what's that?
What the fuck is that?
I want to snipe them with this.
Oh, I got him.
Yo, this weapon is sick.
Load all the gold I got.
They look like ghostbusters.
Am I crazy?
Oh, no, I got hit.
There's going to be so many projectiles on screen.
I don't even know which ones belong to me.
Oh, that's ice and snow falling down here.
Pretty cool.
Before I go down there, let's check out the other side.
Man, look at all the blood.
This game is brutal.
I like the music.
Very ominous.
I need to remember which wand is which.
This is my sniper wand.
I'm going to blow that up.
Shit.
Gotcha.
God, this wand is incredible,
sir.
What the fuck?
Sir?
I think he had a sniper.
I think I was one of those guys before when I got polymorph'd.
Remember?
Okay, what next?
I also have a sniper bitch.
The only issue I have with this wand right now is that there's a bit of a... Like, it shoots up.
Like, look.
Okay, so that's one volley.
Oh, never mind.
It's just me.
I thought I saw something I didn't.
Why did it not get turned into a thingy?
It's a lie.
How much do these do?
Five damage.
The sniper wand does 35.
That is a lot.
So if I hit with this... Wait, does that?
That's going through the snow.
Look.
Oh, wait, I can't.
I need to recharge.
Oh, is that why I didn't turn them into?
Because this costs 30 mana.
Oh, I need absolutely 50 mana.
Oh, I need 30 mana.
If I want to snipe and turn them into a bomb thingy.
We've got a dude down there.
Hit him.
And now he's throwing bombs everywhere.
Tell me he killed himself with that.
Excuse me.
Did you die?
I think he died.
My gold!
Oh, no.
Oh, there was a lot of gold here.
He must have killed a bunch of enemies.
What the hell is that over there?
That's scary.
That's really scary.
Okay.
I really hope I don't get to some kind of level where there's a timer on me.
That will be the worst.
I need to take my time.
That's also the most fun.
Go up here.
What do we see?
It's just a cold nugget lying around.
What the hell?
I don't know what that was.
What was that?
There's something on the floor here.
Yo!
There's a gatling gun.
Are you seeing this?
This is insane.
See ya, bitch.
Holy shit.
This is awesome.
I love this.
I love making spells.
I mean, once.
Another one.
Let's get to safety.
There's another one over there.
I see the light.
Oh, man.
The music is anxiety inducing.
Oh, no.
Wait.
These are... Ghostbusters.
Can I... Excuse me.
Oh, what if I hit you through here?
This is going to be the ultimate play watch.
That's awesome.
Hey, sir.
Bye-bye.
I love my sniper.
I am the one who's still here.
No, no, no.
It's just knives.
What else do we have here?
There's definitely a wand there.
I can't get to it, actually.
I have bombs.
You know what?
Let's do it.
Is this water?
Chili water.
Okay.
Interesting.
Rock and a bomb and some light.
There we go.
Is anything
I'm stuck.
Oh, it's ice.
More bombs.
Drain all that water.
There we go.
What do we got?
Now I can maybe see what this means.
Quantum split.
Makes a projectile split into three projectiles whose existences are entangled.
Say what?
What does that mean?
Does that mean when one of the projectiles does something, the other one does the same thing?
Like if I have a... oh man.
Okay, that gets crazy quick.
What's this?
Poison trail?
Reduce spread.
Okay.
Digging bolt.
A bolt that is ideal for mining operations.
What?
Wait a second.
Ah, that's just poison.
What the fuck?
Projectile?
Manage drain zero.
Wait a minute.
What the fuck?
Reduces the spread.
What am I not getting?
It's just emitting a bunch of poison.
Is that digging?
Huh.
Okay, I'm not sure what that does, so I'm just gonna leave it here.
Because that seems worthless compared to my other one.
Ah, this one.
Yeah, we're gonna keep it like that for now.
Let's see what's up here.
Okay, there's nothing there.
Excuse me.
All right, all right, all right.
You mad?
I understand.
Oh man, this does so much damage.
Hitting with this one?
Almost hit him.
I see him there.
A little lower.
What?
Oh, he's dead?
Oh, he's dead.
Ha, I thought he was alive.
Okay, something's going on down there.
Wait a minute, what's up here?
Nothing.
Okay.
Ah, it's a dude with two hands.
See ya, dude.
I think it's still exploding.
Look at my screen shaking.
Oh, that's a sniper.
Yo, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Oh my god.
How do I... how do I?
How do I, you know?
Wait, what is this?
Concentrated mana.
Water.
Okay, what's the last one?
Levitation.
Oh, you know what?
Let's utilize that.
Levitation.
Sniping time.
Oh yeah, you wanna, you wanna dance?
Where are you?
Oh, geez, shit.
Wow, that hurt.
He does not fuck around.
They have some range.
Gotta.
Haha.
Okay.
Okay, dude.
You have some skills.
Man, my screen is shaking a lot.
I don't know what's happening.
Oh no.
Gotcha.
What's this?
It's just water.
Okay, got a rat over there.
Okay, this is actually sick.
This weapon right here is the tits.
Oh, I didn't see you.
Motherfucker.
Okay, we're losing HP here.
It's getting dangerous.
There's, wait, there's something up there.
Hold on now.
Wait, is this...
poison having dug through here?
Is that what's happening?
Uh-oh.
Gotcha.
Cold and calculated.
That's what I am.
One shot, one kill.
That's dense rock, I believe.
Can't dig through that, but there's stuff up here.
You bastard.
Come here.
I don't like that he goes below me.
What's happening?
What just happened?
Is that frozen steam or something?
Like, what is going on here?
Oh, that is levitation.
Ha.
Fill me up with that.
Okay, this guy's below me.
That means we need to make a rock and a bomb.
Levitation on everybody.
And there's a dude below me there as well.
Oh my god.
I thought that was a gold nugget in the air.
I tried to collect it.
Uh, that thing right there is scaring me.
That is an electricity thing.
How is this game so cool, dude?
Why is it so dark here?
Wait, magical temple?
It feels gloomy in here?
Oh no, I have light only on my bombs.
That's the only way to see.
I should have put my light on this.
Oh, no.
Mistakes were made.
Wow, this thing is still a light.
Look at that.
It's a permanent lighted rock.
What the hell is that?
Large explosive box?
Oh, it's invisible.
Someone is invisible.
I'm burning.
Excuse me.
I think I got him.
There's gold.
The fuck?
Summon large explosive box.
A large box of explosive matter.
Double spell.
What the fuck?
Really?
I just killed a dude who had a wand.
Hey!
Okay.
What the fuck?
You know what?
Let's, uh, hmm.
I don't know if I want that.
You know what?
Fuck it.
I do want that.
I do want it.
Seems cool.
But I don't have a way of exp- no, that's too, that's too fucked.
I'm gonna kill myself with that.
100%.
I will definitely kill myself with that.
Let's not, let's not.
Let's see what's in here instead.
I'm gonna throw a lighted rock.
It's the only way through this dark place.
It's to bomb everything it seems.
Light it up!
That's gonna make the other thing explode.
Whoa!
Okay.
I'm fucking up this temple.
That's what I'm doing.
Okay, just recharge that.
If something's gonna kill me instantly here, I'm gonna- Oh, I'm so scared.
I'm scared!
Oh, man.
This is so exciting.
I need to take a sip.
Okay, okay.
Calm down.
It's gonna be fine.
I hear evil noises.
Oh, wait!
Excuse me.
What's happening there?
Thank God, wherever I've been, it's revealed.
That's really nice.
Reveal, reveal, reveal, reveal.
Okay, everything's fine.
What is that?
That looks nasty.
He has a large snout of some sort.
I'm gonna try and hit him with this.
See ya, bitch!
I got him.
He killed himself.
At least I can see the enemies before they appear in the dark.
At least that's what it looks like to me.
What's happening?
There's a wand, I think?
Is someone invisible again?
Huh?
Look!
I don't like it.
Okay, that's a dead end.
Thank God.
You know what?
I think it's time.
We gotta heal.
Oh, that's not a lot of... Okay, never mind.
It heals more.
Oh, that's fucking awesome.
We're full HP.
Yeah.
I don't like this thing.
I'm scared of it, so I'm not gonna go that way.
I feel like it's gonna blow me up.
It's a trap.
Let's go down here instead.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute now.
What's that?
What's this?
Double scatter, add mana, magic bolt, a powerful magical... That is actually powerful.
13 damage?
Recharged.
Uh, let me try it.
Oh!
Oh, that's cool!
That's a total shotgun.
Puff!
Oh, that's nice.
Actually pretty cool.
I like it.
Wait, is it digging?
Oh, I think it removes snow at least.
Everything does, right?
I think I may want this instead.
They hold it down.
It's kind of a long recharge, but I could put this on another one.
Oh, here's a piece of ice.
Oh, I thought some fucked up transparent monster came at me.
That just messed me up.
Back.
All right, let's keep going.
Let's go down here.
You know what?
What I just did there is a mistake.
What if there was an explosive device in front of me?
The reason I just did that was in case there was an enemy.
But that is way too scary.
That's a new rule.
Don't shoot in the dark when you don't know what's there.
Oh!
Haha!
Oh, the sick dodge!
Who are you?
It's a guy in a rope.
Oh, he dodged that?
Oh my god, I can't hit for shit.
Uh, he's burning now.
Wait, is he immune?
What's happening?
Gotcha.
Thank you.
That was a sick dodge that I just did.
What's that?
Why are people moaning in the background?
Come on.
Okay, there's an enemy there.
What was that sound just now?
Okay, he's shooting some bullshit.
I think I hit something back there.
I'm not sure what I hit.
I missed.
I missed!
Holy shit!
That was, that was...
Pssst!
See ya!
Oh, that was scary.
He has a wand!
Oh my god.
Come here.
I see you.
I see.
Oh, he's coming up there now.
Huh?
I think the wand yourself, uh, exploded.
Self-destruction.
He picked it up!
No way!
My wand.
What the hell is this?
Essence to power increases a projectile's damage based on the number of creatures nearby.
Wow, okay.
Fireball thrower makes a projectile cast fireballs in random directions.
Lightning bolt, the primordial force of nature.
Formation pentagon casts five spells in a pentagonal pattern.
Damn, dude!
All of these seem awesome!
Do I want that in?
Oh, I think I want that instead of this stuff.
But wait, I need to look at the wand.
What is best here?
0.02 cast delay, isn't that like absurdly low?
I feel like that's an absurdly low cast delay.
Uh, but then again, this one has a cast delay that is negative?
Wait, what?
Oh, wait.
Huh?
I don't understand that, but it has a long recharge time.
That's terrible.
Um, right now I have... I want to keep this.
Spells per cast.
You know what?
I'm gonna keep that for now to experiment with later.
Yeah, that's what we're gonna do.
Okay, let's keep moving.
This place is scary.
Okay, slowly reveal everything.
Let me reveal it completely.
There we go.
Uh-oh, there's something.
What's that?
Someone just threw something?
Did I hit something?
Oh yeah.
What the fuck?
Where are you?
Gotcha!
I think what happened, I hit him with this.
He became a fireball emitter and he emitted fireballs and blew up his own fucking things.
He kept throwing at me.
That was sick.
Wow.
Look at this.
Someone exposed the fuck.
What the fuck, dude?
All right.
Well, I am encountering all kinds of shit today.
Okay.
What else we got?
More invisible dudes?
I don't like these explosive things here.
I want to blow them up.
I don't like that.
There's another dude there.
Okay, thank God.
He's dead.
Good.
Where's the other one?
Okay.
Wow.
You do that, huh?
Gotcha.
Dude, are you all right down there?
Wow.
Wait, is he maybe explosion immune?
Is that why he's not dying?
What's happening?
This is kind of a bad situation for me now.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm scared.
My dude, are you all right?
I'm going to try and see if I can snipe him here.
I think I missed.
It stopped.
Did I hit him?
Maybe he died, actually.
He's dead.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
No!
Oh, shit.
Oh, I'm stuck.
My heart rate is completely in the top all the time in this game.
I can't speak English.
Like, my heart is in my throat.
That's a bunch of acid.
I don't like these explosive boxes.
We're going to take care of them.
I missed.
I hit it.
Fucking awesome explosions, by the way.
All the little projectiles flying off everywhere.
So cool.
Ooh, what is this?
Poison.
Oh, another one of those things.
Oh, my God.
I entered question mark.
That
is so scary.
Gold for me.
Okay.
Oh, poison, poison.
Be careful.
Where the fuck am I?
Something's over here.
I heard someone throwing something.
I think.
This looks like a boss arena.
Okay,
there is one there.
I missed.
Oh, my God.
Gotcha.
But that was not the guy shooting me up there.
That was something else.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I gotcha, bitch.
It's just a spark bolt.
Okay.
This is nuts.
I feel like I should maybe heal.
But not quite yet.
Let's lose a little more HP.
There's something in the center of that thing.
Oh, it's like a sick shot.
That was sick.
It's an upside down pyramid type deal, but then not really.
It's like a weirdly shaped thing.
Very mysterious structure there.
What the hell is that?
Gold, I think, actually.
Yeah, it's just gold.
Obviously, there's something in the center of this.
Can't tell what it is.
You heard that?
Someone is throwing something.
We got to blow this up.
I don't have my bombs.
Oh, well, the bombs is just going to roll downhill from here.
This is not going to work.
Fireball.
No,
this ain't going to work, dude.
Bounces right off.
I need to find something destructive.
I have an idea, actually.
I'm going to find one of those wands that emits those explosive boxes.
I'm going to fire them off and then shoot them in the air while they're next to it.
Wait, can I?
Yeah, don't kick that.
I was about to kick it.
What's in this one?
Oh, a bunch of smoke.
Interesting.
This is that one.
No, no, I need the other one that I saw.
What was it?
Huh.
It's somewhere around here.
There's been so many of them.
But you know what for now?
Oh, what's this?
Is that one?
Let's just keep going a little bit.
See what we find.
The hell is this?
A candle, maybe?
Ever glowing?
This place is huge.
There's a wand.
I think that that may be the one that I'm looking for.
Yes, it is.
Oh, what the fuck is that?
Look at that.
Like a skeleton.
Sir, hello.
It's emitting some kind of bullshit and it's not doing anything to me right now, it seems.
Whatever this particle effect is.
Okay, here's what I'm going to do, actually.
Sir, this is for you.
That's for you.
It's all for you.
There we go.
Look at that.
That's all yours.
Oh, no.
I'm scared of kicking that.
I don't trust it.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to blow that up.
Chain reaction.
Shit.
A little higher.
Tell me those are going to explode.
Here we go.
What?
Did he take damage at all?
I'm going to hit him with this with the sniper now.
Whoa.
I think he died.
He's emitting a shit ton of bone dust.
The gold nuggets are out of re- I don't like this.
This is like some weird fucked up chemical reaction.
There's also a wand, actually.
Can I get that?
Let me blow this shit up.
Wait, is there something on the top right?
Oh, it's just a wand.
How did that not do anything?
Oh, it's hitting this little piece of ground, I think.
Oh, no, it's getting stuck in the dust, I think.
Let's go from the left.
Let's see what's here.
Let's try not.
Bam!
Sick.
Oh, it's the same.
Of course, it's that wand.
Of course.
But now I have what I need, so I'm going to go up to that upside down pyramid thing and try it.
Hopefully, it's not going to roll off as easy as I think it will.
Don't stand on that.
What?
Where did you come from?
Sir?
Oh, shit, he's still going.
Maybe he can blow up the thing for me.
He's dead?
Sir?
Did doubts die?
You did.
That's mine.
This is a crazy run so far.
Thomas!
Wait, here we go.
Hmm, that did nothing.
I see markings here.
Very vaguely, I see markings on this thing.
How do I gain access?
Maybe if I just hit it enough.
Hmm, weird.
Weird, weird, weird.
Let's keep moving a little bit.
Oh, don't step in that.
Keep exploring.
I gotta take a step.
This is so scary.
What's that?
What kind of bony material?
Okay.
That looks a lot like that other area I was in.
Yeah, with the boss.
I think a boss is going to appear here.
Oh, no.
That looks like a boss area.
Oh, fuck.
I need to explore.
Oh, what's...
Okay, it's just a piece of furniture.
I'm just glad they don't hide enemies in the dark, and they appear right when you reveal it.
That would be terrible.
At least they should have shown them a little bit beforehand.
So happy about that.
Okay.
This all looks very familiar, actually.
You know what this looks a little bit like?
It looks like that Egyptian place I was in on the surface the other time.
Orb room.
I could just take it and run.
Orb?
What?
There's a tablet.
Okay, pick it up.
Oh, I can't.
Wait.
Uh,
get rid of that.
I'm taking this with me.
I'm scared.
You discovered Orb of True Knowledge, Secrets of Fire, and Brimstone have been unlocked to you.
Holy Bomb.
I got it.
I'm leaving.
I'm out of here.
Thanks.
Please, no boss.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No boss, please.
Okay, let's go to safety here and check that out.
The screen just shook.
I think a boss is coming.
Uh, what did I get?
Holy Bomb.
Someone's a bomb that, well, I guess a holy hand grenade.
Hallelujah.
From worms.
You know what I mean.
Definitely want to try that if I get the opportunity.
Please, no boss.
I think the boss did appear after a bit of time last time as well in the other place.
Oh, I should fight it actually.
I do want to kill a boss.
I have some good weapons.
All the concentrated mana that I spilled is here now.
I'm afraid.
Maybe I'm going to try and go through it.
See what's on the other side.
Run, run, run, run, run, run.
There's nothing.
Okay.
We move on then.
We go back to the snowy cave.
Definitely.
And I, you know what?
I think I should heal.
Play it safe.
There we go.
Maximum HP achieved.
Not bad at all.
I hear someone throwing things still.
Somewhere over here.
Where are you?
Huh?
Where the hell?
You know what actually?
I want this one back.
Give me my bombs.
Infinite bombs is too good to say no to.
Oh,
wait, is he my friend?
He's my friend.
Hey, dude.
Come with me.
We're going on an adventure.
I don't know how you're my friend.
You must have somehow slipped in some liquid.
But that's cool.
It's a pigeon.
And there's a... that's a mage.
Okay, a little lower.
Oh, he's behind the box.
Shit.
I'm going to try and see if I can hit this guy.
Get sniped, fool.
Get the fuck out of here.
I love this spell.
Oh, that guy's still alive.
Come on, friendies.
Kill him.
Yeah, that's it.
Murder him.
Go, go, go.
Attack.
Get him.
He hit me somehow.
They killed him.
Awesome.
Good job, friendos.
What's this?
Chaotic polymorphine.
Oh, oh, also the tablet.
I got to read this.
Put it there.
Let's see here.
Emerald tablet, volume five.
And the Lord spake, saying, first shalt thou take out the holy pin.
Then shalt thou count to three.
No more, no less.
Three shall be the number thou shalt count, and the number of the counting shall be three.
For thou shalt not count, neither count to thou two, excepting that thou then proceed to three.
Five is right out.
Once at the number three, being the third number be reached, then lobbest thou thy holy hand grenade of Antioch's towards thy foe who being naughty in my sight shall snuff it.
Okay, okay, this is obviously half joking, half serious.
I need to lob a holy hand grenade of Antioch towards a foe who being naughty in my sight shall snuff it.
Ah, take out the holy pin of the holy hand grenade.
I get it.
Count to three, no more, no less.
Why do I count to three, though?
You know?
Hmm.
All right.
So I think I actually do want this polymorphine.
So this tablet can go bye-bye, pretty much.
Scrap!
Dude, you can you can throw that with some force.
Yeah, that thing can be used, I think, to do crazy stuff in a pinch.
It's chaotic, too, so I can become anything.
My mom told me I could be anything.
So I became a... I can't remember any of the names of the monsters, the Finnish names.
What's up here?
Dead end.
That's good to know, though.
Come on, buddies.
Let's get a move on.
We have much to do.
Many things to kill, much to explore.
We are only beginning.
So I've been everywhere here.
Hello.
Oh, it's one of those flying jetpack dudes.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, I'm so good.
What is that?
A steel humanoid.
Down you go.
What's over here?
Where's my followers?
They're too slow.
They can't follow me.
This is where I started.
I remember this.
I had poison there.
Oh, someone is throwing things.
I do hear it.
Holy hand grenade of Antioch.
Isn't that a city?
Come on.
Oh, this is where I came in.
Oh, my God, this area is huge.
What the hell?
Much bigger than I thought.
And I was here.
I remember looking at the snow.
It's still rolling downhill.
Man, bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
God, I love this.
I love this game.
Oops.
My God.
I beset on all sides.
It's getting scary.
Oh, my.
I got him.
I fucking hit him.
Look at these things.
They're throwing slimy balls.
I can't hit anything.
I'm terrible.
I got him.
What a shot.
God damn.
I absolutely love the magic lands or whatever.
What is this name?
Blowing lands.
It's so good.
That's the roof.
Oh, I saw something up there.
There is something up there.
There was something up there.
He's now exploded.
Come on.
What's that?
Something's glowing over there on the other side.
Is that an enemy?
It is a robot.
What is this down here?
I don't know what it is, but I kill it.
It's like one of those fire skulls, but it's the opposite.
I took damage from that just now.
Uh-oh.
Oh, my God.
I'm so good.
Don't even hit me with those slimy balls.
Don't think about it.
So there's a dude down here.
Have some light on the boulder.
Another one.
And another.
Oh, things are happening.
Here you go.
This is so exciting.
Okay, let's get rid of that.
I don't trust it.
Aha!
I released the Kraken.
He has a machine gun.
He's gone.
What else can this game offer up for me?
Kill that red.
What the hell is that thing?
What kind of canister?
You know what?
Let's try and shoot it.
Did nothing.
Okay.
Those canisters explode in a freezing vapor.
Wow.
Good to know.
Good thing that I tested that.
Hot damn.
And we've got stuff in here, it seems.
Can I get in there?
I have infinite bombs.
Should be doable somehow.
Maybe not.
But I can definitely do this.
Blow it up.
What have I released?
Show thyself.
I think I hit just... I think I just killed something.
That's a wand.
All right.
What the
God!
I'm scared.
Am I hitting something?
Okay.
He's almost out of range here, but a little higher.
A little lower.
A little higher.
Oh, come on.
Oh, wait.
My projectiles are being slowed inside of his thingy.
I need to go higher.
Sir!
Jesus!
Oh, something is behind me.
Sir, will you calm down?
I'm hitting him.
Oh, come on.
I'm out of mana.
I hit him.
Oh my God, what's happening?
Something just exploded.
I'm hitting him.
Dude, this enemy is insane.
Jesus Christ.
What is happening?
What is this?
Red mist.
Is he dead?
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid to keep going.
When I know he's down there.
I think he's not dead yet.
Let me cut that off.
God, that's so nice.
Being able to do that feels amazing.
Look at that.
Can I die from this?
Imagine if that hits me in the face.
Uh-oh.
That's a sniper, dude.
I'm so scared.
I'm not.
I was kidding.
Oh, goddamn.
What do we got in here?
A dude.
Thank you for the contribution.
A snowman.
I'm scared.
Okay, I'm gonna blow it up because I feel like that's gonna kill me.
Notice how that just penetrated all the way through that wood and into the frost.
Oh my God, come on.
Oh,
I cut through his midsection.
Excuse me.
Hey, wake up.
Dude, come on.
Do something.
Who made you?
How fucking cool is that?
I cut through his midsection.
Midsection with my weapon and then when I kicked him off the thing, they separated like that.
That is just the coolest.
So neat.
Hello.
Please die.
You're dead.
What is that in there?
Hold on.
What do we got here?
I'm not quite sure.
I think whatever it was, it's gone now.
I blew that thing to smithereens.
There's a robot.
I'm stuck.
All my life.
Oh my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I'm slipping.
I'm slipping.
Oh, you got to get out of here.
Where's the portal?
Fuck.
I need to take a sip.
Holy shit.
I saw my life flash before my eyes.
Okay, okay, okay.
We got to get to that wand.
Bomb it.
Who would have known?
Playing with bombs is dangerous stuff.
That was the piece of the robot flying over there.
Look at that majestic looking wand.
Oh, I can't even get to it.
There's sort of things here.
Wait a minute.
Let me douse this.
Better.
What's this?
A new wand.
Looks cool.
Zero degree spread.
21 capacity.
Only one spells per cast.
It does floating arc, electric charge.
Gives the projectile an electric charge that it that it will release on impact.
Magic arrow.
A handy magical arrow.
I mean, we got to try it.
Got to try that.
Huh.
I mean.
Not really that cool.
To be honest with you.
Can we get rid of this ice?
Get out of here.
Oh no, I can't reach this.
I may have to blow it up.
Oh, but I can't without the blow up wand.
Wait, can I cut through the ice?
Cut it.
We're making progress.
There we go.
Looking at shit.
Feels amazing.
So I think in order to progress, I may have to go down.
That's usually where the portals are.
So how about we stop fucking around up here, but oh man, I do want to fuck around so much.
It's so tempting.
Wait, is this guy still down here?
What is that sound?
Oh my God, he's still there.
Did I hit him?
I hit him now.
Here we go again.
I just need to hit him with this every time.
He's immune to explosions, it seems.
I'm definitely doing damage.
I saw damage number.
I missed.
I think I missed.
I hit him.
I hit him again.
Got him.
Man, this guy is no joke.
Are you actually kidding?
I hit him again.
Is he healing?
You know what, you want some bombs?
I'll give you bombs.
Uh, did I get him?
Dude, I think I hit him with the rock and that's what killed him.
Slime mist, a cloud of slimey mist.
That's what he was doing.
So I guess that did indeed slow projectiles around him.
Because when I shot my, uh, illuminating wand or whatever.
No, uh, luminous spear.
Is that what it's called?
Glowing lance.
Oh my God.
When I shot my glowing lance, it arced normally.
And then it fell off quickly when it hit this slime mist.
Man, a charge speed.
Five to five.
Wait a minute.
Isn't that crazy?
Look at this.
All of these have 5845.
This has 500.
That's gotta be insane somehow.
Right?
How about, oh, I don't...
I'm gonna take this.
I'm gonna take a chance.
What's this?
Electric charge.
Uh, yeah, I'm not sure.
I can come back later if I need explosions, I guess.
If I really wanted.
That's a sniper.
Oh, look how it shot through the ice.
That's cool.
Ah, see, now I'm missing my bomb already.
Back we go, back we go.
We got the bomb.
Sir, did you not know that it is illegal?
To throw firearms.
Is he gonna die?
I see him.
I'm sort of aiming where his laser pointer is.
This is a bit risky.
He must... it must be some kind of incline because he never dies to the bomb.
It must... the bomb must be like falling down past him or something.
I could just go for it, but that's scary stuff.
Wait, is he dead?
Did I get him?
Oh, the portal!
I think I got him, dude!
Hell yeah!
What's on the other side?
Nothing.
Fuck yeah, dude, let's go!
This is awesome, dude.
Wait, we don't heal yet.
My god, that's expensive.
Holy shit!
There's all kinds of things!
Wait, I don't know what these are, though.
I can't really inspect them yet.
I think I want this.
But this also looks... why is it so expensive?
This has to be good, then.
If it's that expensive... let's see, this one... 500 mana charge?
I gotta have this.
Uh, which one do I... probably that one.
I can finally change my things as well!
It's gonna be so good!
Uh, wait.
Before I do this, let me, uh, go over here.
Let's drop that... no.
Yes, drop that there for now.
Come over here.
We grab this one, replace it with that, because it sucks!
And we come back.
Oh, I could have just put in my spells, I guess, but whatever.
Okay, uh, there we go.
Let's see what we got here.
We got a rock accelerating... accelerative homing.
It's a projectile modifier.
Homes towards enemies at an increasing pace.
That sounds pretty good.
Bouncing burst, okay.
Magic missile, a fiery explosive projectile.
75 damage.
Man freeze charge.
Gives the projectile a frozen charge that it will release on impact.
Nice.
Summon rock spirit.
I think I've had this one before.
Prickly spore pod?
Summons a spore pod that attaches to a surface and then grows and explodes into spikes.
What?
And pentagon formation.
I am scared to just try to activate this wand.
Look at all the crap, but I guess it's only going to throw the first three for now.
Let's see here.
Oh!
Okay, that hurts me.
Mother crapper.
Wait, why did you just... what just happened?
So, whatever this was that exploded there, isn't that that?
Why is that being used?
So that's being shot.
Oh, this is modifier.
It's modifying this, that, modifier, modifier.
Huh.
Gives a projectile a throat that it will... Ah, this is probably what hit me then.
I think I summoned this.
Actually, I'm not sure what the fuck just happened.
That is very confusing.
I think I should heal no matter what here in case I kill myself.
Because we can always use...
Ah, where is it?
The healing spell to heal ourselves up and then use the recharge.
Wait, we can't because it's out of charges right now, isn't it?
Where is it even?
There, yeah.
Okay, yes, we gotta recharge that.
Okay, so what I'm thinking here immediately, that sounds crazy.
Homing sounds insane.
I could do a homing rock, but I was thinking homing holy bomb.
I kind of want to try the holy bomb.
Wait a minute, we gotta try this.
Let's get rid of these.
Wait, what?
It cost 300 mana.
Whoa.
I can't even use it.
That's crazy.
But wait, this has 130 mana max, 210.
Oh, shit.
Wow, how do I get more?
I guess I get a better wand.
But I was thinking, what if I add mana first?
Is that gonna increase the max, I wonder?
Or it's just gonna like make the spell that comes after use this amount less mana.
Oh, yeah, mana drain minus 30.
So that's exactly what it does.
Perfect.
So now I know that.
So that's not gonna help with this.
Unfortunately, unfortunately, the bomb is definitely great to have there.
I want to try double rock homing.
This is spells cast three.
Holy shit, that was scary.
Brother.
That was really scary.
Holy shit.
I don't know if I like that.
That's kind of insane.
What?
No way.
How about we don't do that?
Damn.
Okay, what I'm thinking though, homing glowing lands.
Now that sounds pretty fucking good, doesn't it?
That sounds incredible.
And then we put this here.
Hold on.
So maybe I'll put this on another wand now, because I'd really love this combination.
This is an amazing combination that I have going there.
I could also use this, I guess, add mana.
So 1.13 recharge time.
The cast delays actually doesn't matter here.
It doesn't really matter.
Modify, modify, modifier.
Oh, but it cast three.
Wait a minute.
0.33.
Maybe I want it in here instead.
Something like that.
Is that even gonna work?
90?
30.
And this has 124.
Oh yeah, it is gonna work, but I need full mana, I guess.
But the recharge is very slow.
So if I can make that even better, let's just try different ones, see which one works best.
That one doesn't even work.
That's sad.
That one?
I have too many spells here, dude.
How about that?
Oh my god.
This is great.
Look at that.
The mana is practically...
What am I limited by?
The recharge.
Okay.
So what if I do this?
Oh, it's too much.
But wait, what if I do this?
Where'd my thing go?
Here.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
Modify, modify, modifier.
It casts three.
So I think all of these are not considered part of the batch.
As far as I understand here, if I do this now, it's still only one.
Why is it not simultaneously cast two?
Oh, wait, I'm an idiot.
I'm an idiot.
No, no, no.
I forgot how this worked.
This is if you don't have enough spells per cast.
I'm an idiot.
It's not even doing what I think it does.
Okay.
Never mind.
I get it.
So let's do... I should put the mana first, no?
Because this one costs 90.
Not that it really matters.
I mean, it's recharging so quick.
That's an insane fucking thing now, isn't it?
It is kind of scary that the enemies explode.
But that's fine.
A frozen charge that it will release an impact?
Let's try this as well.
Huh.
Not bad.
Plus five ice damage.
Cool.
I mean, I'll take it.
That's pretty cool.
I like it.
Luminous drill.
What else can I put on that?
Wait, what is this?
Is it a projectile?
So if I do that, it should shoot both, right?
Or no, it's actually not.
Wait, what?
Oh, but then I have to... if I do this...
Uh, not quite.
Okay.
Never mind.
I don't think I quite understand this one.
Uh, all right.
Multicast.
Crisp is a pentagonal pattern.
How about no?
It sounds a little too crazy.
Now, putting homing on this up here could also be insane, actually.
Wait a minute.
If these all home...
No way.
Projectile modifier.
It's only gonna modify the next batch.
So it's actually not everything.
It's just the first parts.
So it's definitely better here.
This is just... this is the projectile it modifies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep.
Very cool.
Let me see what else there is over here.
I spent a lot of money already, but I can buy one more thing.
This one.
So the only reason I would buy this is because of the stats of the wand, I guess, if they are good.
Nine... what is that song?
I'm hearing a woodpecker.
Man, I charge speed 21.
Let's see here.
Uh... I don't have enough knowledge to know if this is good.
I don't know if it's good.
Wait a minute.
This one is actually the one I had before.
This is... I like these two wands here.
Maybe this one can be modified a little bit somehow.
The last one needs to be the healing one.
Healing.
Maybe I can add something else to the healing.
Actually, no, because the healing is a one-time use thing.
Don't go crazy with that.
Okay.
This one, though.
Magic missile.
Is that both?
That will do both now, I think.
Even though the homing is only going to work on that one.
I think on that one.
Let's see here.
Why is that not even firing?
I don't understand this.
Castile plus one second.
So these are all modifiers, right?
They modify this guy right here.
And the reason I know that is if I remove that, this is not going to home anymore.
It's just going to go in an arc, right?
Oh, cool.
It's a rocket launcher.
Pretty nice.
Seventy-five.
Yo.
Hello, isn't this way better?
Fuck the glowing lance.
Am I insane?
This is actually way better.
Wait, why doesn't that shoot?
Maybe freeze charge doesn't work with the magic missile.
Oh, I don't have enough mana.
Fuck.
What if I do that?
No.
If I remove this, it's going to work.
And it and it's homing now.
But why is that not actually working the way I think it is?
And now we have some light as well.
That's actually not bad.
Not bad at all.
Let's see here.
130 mana max, 70 plus 90, 160 in total.
But then we take off 60.
So it should be enough.
Am I crazy?
Why does this not work?
It does say mana not enough when I click it, right?
It should take off 60 mana from this.
So that's only 30 mana cost on that.
And then... oh wait, does this cost?
Oh, this also costs... let me remove that for a second.
Oh wait, this also costs mana.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need to put this before here then.
No, it's still not enough.
So this removes all costs from that.
But then these two together are gonna cost too much.
Okay, so I simply don't have enough.
Yeah.
RIP.
But this right now makes this one free.
So if I move that, this is gonna cost in total 70 mana.
I think that seems about right.
I have like 30% left when I shoot.
I mean, I have 70% left when I shoot.
Oh wait, I should have 30% left.
But I guess it recharges so quick, it's hard to see.
Okay, I like this one for now.
This is a great wand.
That's a great wand.
The only thing is, recharge time is 0.98.
Can I do that better?
What if I use this wand for that?
We can go nuts here.
Oh, this is still not enough.
Do that instead.
Oh, recharge is too slow though.
Okay, I see.
I see.
But if it's one of those things I only do once in a while, you know, like massive hit, it's not too bad.
But here's the thing.
I do like the idea of putting the explodey thing on someone.
So I think I'll have a glowing lance version.
Like this.
With that on.
And then I'll have another one here that simply does this instead.
You know, this is the wand.
And this is the other wand.
This is the one that makes them go poof and keep exploding because I like that so much.
Yeah, that's cool.
Freeze charge.
I could even put that on.
I think I have man enough for that.
Let's see.
Does that freeze?
It does.
Cool.
Freezes them a little bit.
Can I do anything else there?
That would be awesome.
Give it a burning trail, but nah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't want that.
This is good.
Let's see if it works.
That's the standard stuff.
Nice.
And I can shoot it pretty quick too.
Sort of.
And the best part about this is, if I shoot it once with full mana, just like I had before, it's guaranteed to make them have the explosion as well.
But if I shoot it afterwards, like this, it's just gonna do the damage.
It's not actually gonna explode on them.
That's pretty neat.
So what do I want this wand to be?
I guess the healing wand.
Right?
I don't like this.
I do like the bomb though.
I'll keep that up here.
Let me get rid of this one.
Get rid of that one.
I'll have to try all of them at some point, of course.
Put that there.
And I think I am good to go again.
But the problem is now, I don't have enough to... I don't have any digging potential.
Yikes!
So, how could I do this?
I want one more wand, man.
One more wand.
This costs 25 mana.
If I do this, and I'm careful, that should not throw a bomb.
But the next time... Wait a minute.
No, okay, never mind.
Wait, a homing bomb.
Wait!
Homing bomb?
Wait a minute.
We gotta try this.
Honestly, that's fucking hilarious.
Dude!
That's like homing rock energy, but it also explodes.
Where is it homing to?
Whoa!
That's scary.
Okay, we're not doing that.
Fucking hell!
That is insanity.
No, no, no, no, no.
Maybe we'll have to live without the...
No, the bomb is too useful.
It is too useful.
Maybe I don't want this then.
This seems crazy good, right?
We're gonna try and go without the glowing lands.
I could also remove this one up here.
I'm not a big fan of this, actually.
You know what?
Fuck it all.
I have decided.
I don't use this that much anyway.
We're getting rid of all this.
I don't have room for it anyway.
Away you go.
And this wand right here is actually pretty cool.
Let's try this.
Whoa!
Fuck yeah!
I forgot about that.
It has that effect on it.
Oh yeah, we're doing that.
We're doing that!
Hold on.
And now I can even do this.
Oh yeah!
It's gonna have enough mana.
We can even add this, just to be sure.
And then add more.
Add more.
Light.
Light as well.
Oh yeah!
Long recharge though.
Wait, what's just happened?
Why did it shoot like that?
Oh, I don't like that.
What's happening?
Is it this?
Huh?
Is it the mana that I added?
What happened here?
It is?
That's weird.
Huh?
Okay, I don't understand that, but that's okay.
It's fine.
That's okay.
This can be the bomb wand did.
This one down here.
And then this one can be this, where we add the...
Let's do this instead.
This is gonna be the amazing wand there.
We could actually put more on it.
Oh, this is too fun.
I don't know what to do.
Yeah, that's good.
And this one is gonna be that.
If I want to hit someone and make them a living exploding bomb.
Right?
And we have the bomb wand down here.
And the bomb wand, do I want to add anything else to that?
Anything else to that bomb maybe?
I don't know.
Oh, wait a minute.
No.
Although... bomb.
I do kind of like the rock coming with it.
But it's not coming with it now.
Why is that?
25 mana, 100.
And this has one mana short.
Wow.
So that's why.
Okay.
Well, I guess we leave the rock here.
Let's go.
I'm gonna save my money.
Save the money.
What do we got here now?
Teleportitis.
You take 20% less damage.
You teleport away every time you're hurt.
Now that sounds way too chaotic for me.
Close call.
You gain additional chance to deal critical hits as long as there are enemies near you.
I mean, that's always gonna be the case, isn't it?
Glass cannon.
Your spells are five times as powerful.
But your maximum health becomes 50 and cannot be increased.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're gonna use this!
Extra item in holy mountain.
There will be an additional item in every holy mountain you haven't discovered yet.
Oh, this is the holy mountain.
Worm attractor.
Worms find you attractive.
Low recoil.
Recoil caused by your spells is greatly reduced, but your spells fly slightly slower.
Hmm.
I don't mind the recoil too much.
That's fine with me.
I feel like this could be worms.
They're gonna be my friends instead, right?
Extra item.
I don't really like that either.
I could do another.
I'm gonna do another.
Greed.
You gain double the gold per nugget.
Wand radar.
You can sense nearby wands.
Exploding gold.
Gold dropped by enemies explodes when it disappears.
It's picked up or touched by other enemies.
Enemies can pick up gold?
That's hilarious.
I don't want any of these, honestly.
Maybe just this one.
More gold.
Sense nearby wands is also kind of cool, I guess.
Yeah, let's have more gold.
Greed.
I kind of wish you could go back and take the worm attraction thingy.
Uh, there's a guy right there.
Let me remind myself what spells I have.
I have this one.
I don't know if this does friendly fire.
Oh!
Bro, I wasn't ready.
That's cheating.
Huh?
It's useless.
Why is my wand now shit?
Why is it aiming down?
Wait, is it because there's an enemy below me?
There's an enemy that way, I think.
He's the base.
The fuck are these?
Flying servo racks.
Excuse me?
Uh... Whoa!
Man, this weapon sucks now!
What the hell?
Why is it flying like that?
This is useless.
Gotcha.
Oh my god!
I'm stuck!
Oh shit!
I regret my wand choices.
The first wand sucks dick.
I will not use that at all.
It's horribly...
You can't count on it at all.
This thing right here is messing it up.
Somehow.
It's bad.
It's real bad.
Uh, the last one is the bomb.
That's decent.
It's a bomb.
That makes sense.
So what I want is this one in my first.
And... Wait, I can go back and change my... Yeah.
I'm blowing this shit up.
I'm changing my wand.
I can still do it.
Don't burn.
Okay, okay.
Not bad.
Am I crazy or do I hear singing bowls?
Uh...
I don't like that knocking sound.
Makes me uneasy.
Okay.
Give me... Oh wait, there's nothing in this one.
Oh, but I can pick these up.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, that's gonna take a while though.
All right.
Oh no, I can't change anything anyway.
Mmm...
Fuck it.
I'll leave it here.
Whatever.
I can make do with my wand that I have.
I can make do with this one.
My trusty luminous arrow.
That thing's gonna explode into a frosty mist.
Look at these fools down there.
I'm gonna leave them in there.
That seems like a deadly bunch.
Oh, the recharge on this is so good compared to before.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
Easy base.
I'm invading their base.
Base invasion.
He's dead.
I do kind of want to blow these fools up in there somehow.
Uh...
What the?
Is that a trap?
Oh!
What's happening?
I clicked too late.
I can't see what happened.
Oh no.
Here's my theory.
I think that bobble, when you hit it with a spell, that spell is reflected back on you.
And when that thing hit me, I got hit by the arrow and I started exploding.
Constantly, just like my enemies.
That's what I think happened.
Yep.
That's my guess on that.
But look at all these records, huh?
Almost three hour run on that.
Isn't that amazing?
Places visited eight.
That's double what I had before.
More than double my enemy slain.
And a lot of max hp, 40 items found.
And one orb collected.
Total wins zero.
Yeah, I haven't won yet.
But that was awesome.
Progress.
Let's see here.
Oh, look at all this stuff.
I want to see if I can't find those... this one.
Stendari.
Say it to you.
Uh, what's that?
Uh...
Snippuhisi.
Oh!
Heezy base.
Snippuhisi.
Heezy and Sniper.
Whatever Heezy means.
Right.
Okay.
And...
I discovered a bunch of perks.
I have... wait, I found three secrets.
Did I?
I mean, have I?
In total, found three secrets?
What are the secrets?
Hmm.
Maybe one of them was behind the lava that I went, you know?
Dude, this is way too good.
That was a great run.
Fuck yeah.
That was fun.
I'm gonna take the worm with me now.
Because I want to try it in the wild.
And this time I will not get cursed.
I swear I will just pick up the worm and be on my way.
What do I have?
Spark bolts and bombs.
A classic setup.
And what is this?
It's just water.
Gotcha.
Why is this sort of, uh...
What is in here?
I bet you there's a secret down there somewhere.
Yeah, it's gotta be.
In fact, I just heard an enemy.
I heard someone throwing again.
Huh?
Oh!
Oh yeah.
Oh, dick for me.
Dick for... Yes, dick for... What's this?
Concentrated mana.
Dick for me.
Go, come on.
Dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick.
Yeah.
Look at you making a little rout for me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Keep going, keep going.
Yes.
Oh!
Sir, calm down.
And he comes back like that?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Sir, will you be my friend?
Go.
Oh, it's just doing that.
Oh, no!
I knew that would happen.
Fuck worm bite.